A Finding Aid to the Ankrum Gallery Records, circa 1900-circa 1990s, bulk 1960-1990, in the Archives of American Art AAA.ankrgall
Archives of American Art
- Artists’ Files, 1957-1994; Series 5; 22.2 Linear feet Boxes 3-25, 41-42
  - Johnson, Buffie, circa 1980-1982 (Box 12, Folder 11-12)
  - Johnson, Mac, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Johnson, Oliver, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Jordan, Conrad, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Jordy, Michael, 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Kane, Bob, 1968-1990 (Box 12, Folder 17-20)
  - Kanemitsu, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Karoy, K., circa 1987 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Karpel, Eli, 1968-1988 (Box 12, Folder 23-31)
  - Kepenyes, Pal, 1964-1965 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Kestenbaum, Lothar, circa 1961-1966 (Box 12, Folder 33-35)
  - Kim, Tschang-Yeul, 1978-1981 (Box 13, Folder 1-4)
  - Kipniss, Robert, 1961-1965 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Kirszencwajg, Sam, circa 1970 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Kisch, Gloria, 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder 7-8)
  - Kleanthis (Clyde Baxter), circa 1965 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Kleinert, Peter, circa 1960-circa 1980 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Kline, Franz, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Knutson, Rod, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Koblick, Freda, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Kondos, Gregory, 1973-1975 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Kovarsky, Yehoshua, 1957-1965 (Box 13, Folder 15-16)
  - Kramer, Albert, 1968-1974 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Krauss, Anthony, circa 1986-1993 (Box 13, Folder 18-19)
  - Kreitzer, David, 1968-1987 (Box 13, Folder 20-27)
  - Kroll, Rolfe, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Kristianson, Linda, 1971-1974 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Kuper, Rose, 1968-1972 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Kussoy, Bernice, circa 1961-1964 (Box 13, Folder 31-34)
  - Kussoy, Bernice, circa 1961-1984 (Box 14, Folder 1-16)
  - Kyle, George, 1982-1986 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Labby, Sherman, 1968-1970 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Laborice, Hugo, 1984-1986 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - La Duke, Betty, 1968-1970 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Laidman, Roberta, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Lande, Henry, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Lane, Doyle, 1965-1967 (Box 14, Folder 23-25)
  - Lanes, Gretchen, 1987-1994 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Larson, Lynn, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Lawrence, Jacob, circa 1974 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Lawrence, Michael, circa 1975 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Lazarevich, Emil, 1961-1965 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Lazarevich, Emil, circa 1962-1990 (Box 15, Folder 1-4)
  - Lebrun, Rico, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Lessing, Janel, 1962-1968 (Box 15, Folder 6-8)
  - Levine, Edward, circa 1975 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Levine, Eleanor, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Lewis, Samella, 1968-1976 (Box 15, Folder 11-14)
  - Lidow, Leza, circa 1980-1989 (Box 15, Folder 15-17)
  - Lieberman, Harry, circa 1968-1991 (Box 15, Folder 18-25)
  - Lieberman, Harry, circa 1965-1991 (Box 16, Folder 1-5)
  - Liu, Kuo-Sung, 1963-1973 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Loew, David, 1962-1972 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Logan, Gene, circa 1969-1990 (Box 16, Folder 8-17)
  - Lowe, Marilyn, circa 1974-1990 (Box 16, Folder 18-20)
  - Lucas, Hank, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Lumpkins, William, 1965-1968 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Lundeberg, Helen, 1963-1968 (Box 16, Folder 23-26)
  - Lundeberg, Helen, 1963-1968 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - MacDonald, James, 1961-1962 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - MacLsay, Jean, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - MacWeeney, Leslie, 1961-1963 (Box 17, Folder 4-5)
  - Mancini, John, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Mandel, Trude, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Manley, Phyllis, circa 1970-1991 (Box 17, Folder 8-13)
  - Marcus, Marcia, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Marin, Sutter, circa 1961 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Maring, Andrew, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Marshall, Kathleen, 1984-1988 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Martir, Agustin Ramos, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Martin, Johnathan, 1987-1989 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Marx, Marcia, 1969-1971 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Masteller, Barry, 1984-1986 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Matthews, Martha, 1984-1988 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Mayers, Gary, circa 1983-1989 (Box 17, Folder 23-24)
  - McCabe, Lawrence, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - McClure, Tom, 1983-1987 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - McIntyre, Ronald, circa 1988 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - McKiernan, Janet, circa 1987 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - McLarty, Barbara, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Melikian, Mary, 1970-1972 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Mesches, Arnold, 1964-1967 (Box 18, Folder 2-3)
  - Micossi, Mario, 1976-1978 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Miller, Henry, 1962-1963 (Box 18, Folder 5-6)
  - Millier, Arthur, circa 1960-1974 (Box 18, Folder 7-10)
  - Millier, Arthur, Negatives of Artwork, circa 1960-circa 1970 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Mitchel, Clark, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Mooney, Malcolm, 1986-1989 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Moore, Elena, 1966-1969 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Morales, Maurice, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Moreno, Miguel, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Moseley, Spencer, 1961-1964 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Munselle, Peter, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Nagai, Iku, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Nagano, Karen, 1983-1985 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Navarro, Josep, circa 1983-1990 (Box 18, Folder 20-21)
  - Nelson, Andy, circa 1965-1993 (Box 18, Folder 22-30)
  - Nelson-Tsukamoto, Keiko, circa 1983 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Nesbitt, John, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Newcombe, Warren, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Nivola, Constantino, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Newell, Gordon, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Obermayr, Raymond, 1972-1974 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Oda, Mayumi, 1974-1982 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Okimoto, Jerry Tsukio, circa 1986 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Olsen, Pomm, circa 1984 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - O’Mara, Michael, 1983-1989 (Box 19, Folder 6-7)
  - Onno, Mai, 1961-1966 (Box 19, Folder 8-9)
  - Orban, Desiderius, 1964-1966 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Organ, Elizabeth, 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Oxley, Harold, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Overstreet, Joe, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Pace, Gloria, undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Padovano, Anthony, 1970-1972 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Pajand, William, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Paladin, David, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Parkinson, Ariel, 1962-1963 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Pendergast, Marguerite, 1970-1973 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Peraza, Humberto, 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Pereny, Madeline, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Peter, Dean, 1970-1974 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Petersen, Harold, 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Petersen, Roland, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Peterson, Kerrie, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Picasso, Pablo, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Pickerill, Bill, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Plazzotta, Enzo, 1977-1979 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Pongdam, Prayat, undated (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Posa, Andrew, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Powell, Fred, circa 1983 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Price, Joe, circa 1977-1989 (Box 19, Folder 32-36)
  - Prins, Pierre, circa 1974 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Prochazka, Oldrich, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Rahmi, Bedri Eyuboglu, 1962-1969 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Rattner, Abraham, 1961-1964 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Reed, Jim, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Remfry, David, 1979-1992 (Box 19, Folder 42-43)
  - Remfry, David, circa 1979-1992 (Box 20, Folder 1-2)
  - “Rhino Horn Group”, 1970-1974 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Riccio, Joseph, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Riddle, John, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Riggle, Alan, 1968-1970 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Robinson, Douglas, 1974-1986 (Box 20, Folder 7-8)
  - Robinson, Leo, circa 1975 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Rocchia, Peter, 1970-1972 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Rogers, Peter, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Rose, Jean, 1979-1990 (Box 20, Folder 12-13)
  - Rosenak, Carol, circa 1985-1990 (Box 20, Folder 14-15)
  - Rosenbaum, John, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Rousseau, Irene, 1969-1971 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Rubadoux, Craig, 1979-1982 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Russell, James, 1979-1990 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Saar, Betty, 1966-1967 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Sanso, 1966-1974 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Sawka, Jan, circa 1976-1985 (Box 20, Folder 22-28)
  - Schirmer, Raffaela, 1980-1989 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Schmeider, Carla, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Schuler, Melvin, 1966-1987 (Box 20, Folder 31-33)
  - Schuler, Melvin, circa 1967-1989 (Box 21, Folder 1-17)
  - Schurman, Mary, 1985-1990 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Schwaderer, Fritz, circa 1962-1986 (Box 21, Folder 19-22)
  - Schwartz, Leonard, 1971-1974 (Box 21, Folder 23-26)
  - Schoeberlein, Liz, 1968-1974 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Scott, Jane Wooster, circa 1973-1986 (Box 22, Folder 1-3)
  - Scoville, Jonathan, 1969-1973 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Secunda, Arthur, circa 1962-1967 (Box 22, Folder 5-8)
  - Seldis, Edward, 1965-1967 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Seeholzer, Werner, 1974-1977 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Seyle, Robert, circa 1962-1975 (Box 22, Folder 11-19)
  - Shahn, Ben, 1971-1976 (Box 22, Folder 20-21)
  - Shang, Stewart, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Shapiro, Brian, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Shepherd, William, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Sheridan, Noel, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Shiokava, Kenzi, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Shores, Ken, 1970-1972 (Box 22, Folder 27-28)
  - Showalter, Max, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 29-30)
  - Silverman, Jack, 1975-1980 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Siro (Harvey Shapiro), 1984-1986 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Smith, Howard, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Smith, James Steel, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Snooks, A. Nancy, 1971-1973 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Sontag, Chris, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Spencer, Jeffrey, 1976-1984 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Starbird, Kenneth, 1969-1970 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Steele, Emily, 1974-1990 (Box 23, Folder 9-19)
  - Stein, Mari, 1978-1984 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Steinberg, Ruben, 1969-1974 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Steiner, Florian, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Stern, Jan Peter, circa 1966-1969 (Box 23, Folder 23-26)
  - Stern, Geraldine, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Stringer, Terry, circa 1982-circa 1990 (Box 23, Folder 28-31)
  - Suby, Alain, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Sugano, Juzo, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Swenson, Karl, 1972-1974 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Swiggett, Jean, 1984-1987 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Takayama, Michio, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Tanner, Henry O., 1973 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Temple, Brooke, 1968-1969 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Tessler, Bennie, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Thall, Victor, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Thompson, Leland, 1969-1970 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Tidball, John, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Tichy, Andrea, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Tobey, Mark, 1962-1980 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Tobias, Robert, 1981-1987 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Tobias, Susa Frost, 1985-1987 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Tomasch, Elmer, 1962-1965 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Tribe, Barbara, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Trigg, Leota, 1968-1969 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Trissel, James, 1976-1979 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Tsuchidana, Harry, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Turner, Charles, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Ulrich, undated (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Upshaw, Lucius, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Van der Heide, Kathinka, 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Van Muejen, Peter, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Van Wagoner, Dick, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Varda, Jean, 1959-1991 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Varner, Kraig, 1987-1991 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Vernon, Alex, 1969-1971 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Virgona, Hank, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Vitale, Anne, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Von Wattenwyl, Peter, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Vu, Michel, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Wakeham, Duane, circa 1974-1988 (Box 24, Folder 26-30)
  - Warne, William, 1979-1985 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Washington, Timothy, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Weber, Stephanie, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Weidman, Phil, 1965-1967 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Weimerskirch, Robert, circa 1970-1990 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Weisbrich, Les, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Weiss, Stephan, 1982-1984 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Wheelden, Michael, circa 1987-1990 (Box 24, Folder 38-39)
  - Wheeler, James, 1983-1985 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Wight, Frederick, 1965-1970 (Box 24, Folder 41-43)
  - Winters, Jonathan, circa 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 1-5)
  - Wrege, Ernest, 1984-1990 (Box 25, Folder 6-7)
  - Wright, Bill, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Wyatt, Richard, 1977-1979 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Yoakum, Delmer, 1978-1979 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Young, Ronald D., 1984-1987 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Zadikian, Zadik, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Zajac, Jack, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Zar, Jim, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Ziegler, Laura, 1974-1986 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Zev, circa 1968-1971 (Box 25, Folder 16-18)
  - Zimmerman, Bernard, 1962-1966 (Box 25, Folder 19-20)
  - Zupan, Bruno, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Oversized Material, Shirl Goedike, from Box 9, Folders 23-37 (Box 41)
- Collector and Client Files, 1960-1994; Series 6; 3.2 Linear feet Boxes 25-28
  Collector and client files document the gallery's relationship with over 115 individuals, museums, and art centers and associations. Files may include correspondence, printed materials, invoices and sales records, and shipping and mailing receipts. Included are Olga and Joseph Hirshhorn and the Hirshhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden, the Krannert Art Museum, Laguna Art Museum, Palm Spring Desert Museum, Paramount Pictures, San Diego Museum of Art, Staempfli Gallery, and Storm King Art Center, among others.
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  - Adams, Hal, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - American Academy of Arts and Letters, 1967-1976 (Box 25, Folder 23-24)
  - Andrews, Mary and Dana, 1962-1965 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Arthur Elrod Associates (Steve Chase Associates), 1967-1988 (Box 25, Folder 26-30)
  - Berrett Galleries, 1981-1986 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Bixer, Ed, 1961-1962 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Brandman, Saul, 1968-1970 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Bray, John Kelly, 1969-1971 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Brown-Buckley, Inc., 1969-1976 (Box 25, Folder 35-36)
  - Burbank Studios, 1968-1973 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Cannel and Chaffin, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Citrus College, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Civic Center Gallery, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Clerk, Dorothy, 1969-1970 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Colorado Springs Fine Arts Center, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Columbia Pictures, 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Contemporary Crafts, Inc., 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - De Mille, Agnes, 1970-1987 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Denver Art Museum, 1968-1979 (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Des Moines Art Center, circa 1970 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Diogenes International Galleries, 1970-1971 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - DMJM, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Dorian Hunter Gallery, 1966-1968 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Downey Museum of Art, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Downtown Gallery (Edith Halpert), 1962-1970 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Findlay Galleries, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Forum Gallery, 1963-1964 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Fresno Art Center, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Fullerton Art League, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Gallery Dache, 1966-1967 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Gallery East, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Glazer, Jules, 1963-1982 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Goldwyn Studios, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Greenberg, Lowell, 1964-1970 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Hauswedell and Nolte, 1974-1985 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Heninger, Helen (Kennedy Galleries Inc.), 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Helm, Frances and MacKinley, 1961-1964 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Hewitt, Mary Jane, 1969-1970 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Highland Gallery of Sculpture, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Hirshhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden (Joseph Hirshhorn), circa 1960-1990 (Box 26, Folder 21-31)
  - Hoffman, Nancy, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Holloway, Sterling, 1961-1964 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Humboldt Cultural Center, 1977-1980 (Box 26, Folder 34-35)
  - International Gallery, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Johnson, Deane, 1969-1977 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Josselyn, Mrs. H. H., 1970 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Kaiser Center for Technology, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Kalamazoo Institute of Arts, 1962-1985 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Kennedy, Edward M., 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Kramer, Rabbi Bill, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Krannert Art Museum, 1962-1979 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Kushner, Victor and Mark, 1970-1974 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Laguna Art Museum, 1964-1989 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - La Jolla Museum of Contemporary Art, 1972-1975 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Lawrence, Fonya and Marc, 1961-1969 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Leidner, Suzanne, 1974-1976 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Los Angeles County Museum of Art, 1986-1990 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Mahoney, Lewis, 1979-1983 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Marie Ganee, Ltd., 1973 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Martha Jackson Gallery, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Martin, Jack, 1970-1975 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Michel, Marten, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Mitchell Museum, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Moringiello, Thomas, 1974-1982 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Morrow, Pat, 1973-1977 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Munsell, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Collection, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Nelson, Andrew (J. Walter Thompson Company), 1966-1967 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Oakland Museum, 1971-1980 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Office of the Secretary of the State of California, circa 1970s (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - O’Neal, Edward, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Pacificulture-Asia Museum, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Palm Springs Desert Museum, 1976-1980 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Paramount Pictures, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Pasadena Art Museum, 1965-1972 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Pattiz, Hap, 1969-1972 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Paul, Jillian, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Pennock, Ted, 1970-1971 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Percival Galleries, 1970-1973 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Perenchio, Inc., 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Perutz, George, 1970-1971 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Phoenix Art Museum, 1963-1982 (Box 27, Folder 32-34)
  - Pride, Inc. (Gallery), 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Provine, Dorothy, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Reiss-Davis Clinic, 1965-1966 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Riverside Art Association, 1966-1969 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Robinson, Irwin, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Rosenstein, Neil, 1970-1973 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Rubin, Henry, 1961-1966 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Salinger, Pierre, 1969-1970 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - San Bernardino County Museum, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - San Diego Museum of Art, 1966-1988 (Box 27, Folder 44-46)
  - San Francisco Museum of Art, 1965-1967 (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - Santa Barbara Museum of Art, 1965-1986 (Box 27, Folder 48-49)
  - Scripps College, 1962-1966 (Box 27, Folder 50)
  - Seldis, Henry, 1961-1974 (Box 27, Folder 51)
  - Smith, James A., 1973 (Box 27, Folder 52)
  - Smithsonian Institution, 1971-1980 (Box 27, Folder 53)
  - Solotoy, Jan, 1970-1989 (Box 27, Folder 54)
  - Sotheby, Parke-Bernet, 1975-1986 (Box 27, Folder 55)
  - Springville Museum of Art, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 56)
  - Staempfli Gallery, 1970-1988 (Box 28, Folder 1-10)
  - Stevens, Arnold, 1969-1974 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Storm King Art Center, 1970-1971 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Synanon Foundation, Inc., 1968-1969 (Box 28, Folder 13-16)
  - Tom Maddock Gallery, 1979-1984 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Universal City Studios, Inc., 1975-1979 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - University of Arizona, 1966-1967 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - University of California’s Conference Center, 1964-1966 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - University of Judaism, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1965-1966 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Waldbridge, Norton and Barbara, 1968-1979 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Warring, Helen, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Weatherspoon Art Gallery, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Werner, Newton, 1967-1988 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Windom, Barbara, 1971-1978 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Witlin, Dr. A., 1967-1971 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Ziv, William, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Various Collectors and Clients, 1968-1994 (Box 28, Folder 30)
- Financial Material, 1962-1990; Series 7; 1.5 Linear feet Boxes 28-30
  Financial materials include numbered sales invoices. consignment records, loan documentation, and insurance valuations.
  - Consignments, 1962-1975 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Gallery Loans, 1963-1975 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Gallery Loans, 1965-1975 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Insurance Valuation, 1981-1986 (Box 29, Folder 2-3)
  - Invoices, 1965-1990 (Box 29, Folder 4-28)
  - Invoices, 1977-1990 (Box 30, Folder 1-12)
- Printed Material, 1957-1994; Series 8; 2 Linear feet Box 30-32, 41
  Printed material consists of periodicals, catalogs and bulletins, exhibition materials, and newspaper and magazine clippings.
  - Catalogs and Bulletins, 1957-1966 (Box 30, Folder 13-14)
  - Exhibition Materials, 1960-1980 (Box 30, Folder 15-19)
  - Exhibiton Materials, 1960-1986 (Box 31, Folder 1-11)
  - General Printed Material, 1971-1975 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Magazine Clippings, circa 1960-1985 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper Clippings, circa 1962-1980 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Periodicals, circa 1960s-1986 (Box 31, Folder 15-19)
  - Periodicals, circa 1960-1990 (Box 32, Folder 1-6)
  - Various Museum Bulletins, circa 1960-1980s (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Oversized General Printed Material from Box 31, Folder 12 (Box 41)
- Scrapbook, 1960-1988; Series 9; 3 Folders Box 32
  One unbound scrapbook contains clippings and exhibition announcements, postcards, and brochures.
  - Unbound Scrapbook, circa 1960-1988 (Box 32, Folder 8-10)
- Photographs, circa 1960s-circa 1990s; Series 10; 0.35 Linear feet Box 32, 42
  Photographs consist of slides, negatives, snapshots, and copyprints depicting primarily artists, artwork, Joan Ankrum, and gallery openings and exhibitions.
  - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1960s-circa 1990s (Box 32, Folder 11-13)
  - Negatives of Artwork, circa 1960s-circa 1990s (Box 42, Folder 2-3)
  - Gallery Photographs, circa 1960s-circa 1990s (Box 32, Folder 14-16)
- Joan Ankrum Personal Papers, circa 1900-1993; Series 11; 2 Linear feet Box 32-34, 41
  This series documents personal and professional activities of Joan Wheeler Ankrum as an actress and gallery owner through correspondence with family and artists; papers regarding sons David and Cary Ankrum, second husband William Challee, and brother Nelson Wheeler; writings by Joan Wheeler Ankrum and mother, financial material, printed material, loose scrapbook material, family and personal photographs, and artwork and sketches from other artists.
  - Correspondence, 1924-circa 1989 (Box 32, Folder 17-21)
  - Correspondence, circa 1960s-1993 (Box 33, Folder 1-8)
  - Illustrated Correspondence, circa 1960s-circa 1980s (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Passport, circa 1959 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Autographs Book, 1924 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Writings, circa 1900-circa 1980s (Box 33, Folder 12-13)
  - Cary Ankrum, circa 1960-1975 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - David Ankrum, 1968-1975 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - William Challee, 1926-1989 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Nelson Wheeler, 1967-1989 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Financial Material, 1962-1987 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Printed Material, circa 1900-circa 1980s (Box 33, Folder 19-20)
  - Loose Scrapbook Material, circa 1931-1977 (Box 34, Folder 1-2)
  - Photographs, circa 1900-circa 1990s (Box 34, Folder 3-9)
  - Artwork from Other Artists, circa 1960s-circa 1980s (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Oversized Loose Scrapbook Material from Box 34, Folders 1-2 (Box 41)
  - Oversized Photographs from Box 34, Folders 3-9 (Box 41)
- Morris Broderson Papers, 1941-1989; Series 12; 7.2 Linear feet Box 34-42
  This series is arranged as 11 subseries.
  12.1: Biographical Material, 1961-1989
  12.2: Correspondence, 1951-1986
  12.3: Publicity Files, circa 1960s-1988
  12.4: Travel, circa 1961-1970
  12.5: Project Files, 1963-1989
  12.6: Exhibition Files, 1961-1994
  12.7: Collector and Client Files, 1960-1990